Don T. Young Photographic Negatives MS088
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Don T. Young negatives, college events, 1963 -- 1981; 1965 -- 1981; MS088.001; 1.5 Linear Feet
  - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts basketball at U-Mass (Boston), Nov. 26, 1978.
    - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015.00002 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015.00003 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Tufts basketball at U-Mass (Boston), Nov. 26, 1978. Slot 4-6: Football team/groups, August 8, 1978. Slot 7: Pop Houston and Hester Sargent Awards, May 12, 1978.
    - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015.00005 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Pop Houston and Hester Sargent Awards, May 12, 1978. Slot 2-7: Football vs. Trinity, Sept. 16, 1978.
    - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015.00006 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-4: Football vs. Trinity, Sept. 16, 1978. Slot 5-7: new football coach, July 13, 1978.
    - Negatives, 1978; MS088.001.001.00015.00007 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: New football coach, July 13, 1978.
  - Negatives, 1980; MS088.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1980; MS088.001.001.00016.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Gestures of baseball catcher (Tufts vs. Harvard) and of Cuitin and Allard, May 2, 1980.
    - Negatives, 1980; MS088.001.001.00016.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: Gestures of baseball catcher (Tufts vs. Harvard) and of Cuitin and Allard, May 2, 1980. Slot 6-7: Coach-of-year award to Vic Gatto, 10/15/1980.
    - Negatives, 1980; MS088.001.001.00016.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-5: Tufts champions awards, Oct. 18, 1980.
  - Negatives, 1981; MS088.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1981; MS088.001.001.00017.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Scrimmage with Framingham State.
    - Negatives, 1981; MS088.001.001.00017.00002 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, 1981; MS088.001.001.00017.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-3: Scrimmage with Framingham State. Slot 4: Tufts University football team, Sept. 12, 1981. Slot 5: Tufts football coach and captain, Sept. 12, 1981. Slot 6: Award to Rocky Carzo, Nov. 12, 1981. Slot 7: copies from archives, August 1981.
    - Negatives, 1981; MS088.001.001.00017.00004 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: "Jumbo Stamped," May 26, 1981. Slot 2-3: copy negatives for Dr. Shulman and Paul Unwer, September 1981.
  - Negatives, n.d., MS088.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - Negatives, n.d., MS088.001.001.00018.00001 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-6: Unlabeled.
    - Negatives, n.d., MS088.001.001.00018.00002 (Box 1)
      Slot 1-7: Tufts Lacrosse.
    - Negatives, n.d., MS088.001.001.00018.00003 (Box 1)
      Slot 1: Tufts Lacrosse. Slot 2: unlabeled.
  - Tufts Golf Tourney 150th Anniv. Game and Parade. Commencement Pictures, 1963; MS088.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    The date of the anniversary is questionable.
  - Tufts U. Football Pictures, Part 1., 1963; MS088.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Football Pictures, Part 2., 1963; MS088.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Tufts "Santa" Pictures, 1963; MS088.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Wrestling Photos, 1964; MS088.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Wrestling Team, 1964; MS088.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Exchange Students, 1964; MS088.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Baseball, 1964; MS088.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Baseball, 1964; MS088.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Paul Rich and wife, Bill Tigke and wife during testimonial for Tigke, 1964; MS088.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Publication Department, New Language Instructor, 1965; MS088.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Baseball - Major Leaguers in Cage., 1965; MS088.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Tufts vs. Brandeis plus Alumni pictures, 1965; MS088.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Basketball vs. Amherst, 1965; MS088.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Paul Rich - Peter Smith Track Pictures, 1965; MS088.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Tufts. Carl Miller Elephant at New Library, 1965; MS088.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Tufts. Filene Center Pictures taken by Paul Rich., 1965; MS088.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Tufts. Golf Champion Billy Carroll, 1965; MS088.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Tufts. U. Tim Ring - Sports Banquet, 1965; MS088.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Tufts. U. Girl Traveler, 1965; MS088.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Student and teacher in Cap and Gown., 1965; MS088.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Golf, 1965; MS088.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Football Co-Captians and Coach Arlansan at New Library., 1965; MS088.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    May-June 1965
  - Tufts Alumni Golf Tourney at Colonial CC, 1965; MS088.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Coaches return - after illness, 1965; MS088.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Tufts College Football Portraits - rejects, 1965; MS088.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Tufts College Football Portraits, 1965; MS088.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Paul Rich Installing Name on New Library, 1965; MS088.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Tufts U. Setups for ads, 1965; MS088.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Basketball, 1965; MS088.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Press Conference for Harry Arlanson, Varsity Football Coach, 1965; MS088.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Wrestling, 1965; MS088.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Swimming, 1965; MS088.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Basketball vs. Harvard., 1965; MS088.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Tufts New Football Coach, 1966; MS088.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - basketball 66 2-21-1-4, 1966; MS088.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Track 66 2-26-1-Team Tufts vs. Colby, 1966; MS088.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Wrestling 66 2-26 11-14 35-37 Tufts vs. Coast Guard, 1966; MS088.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Tennis 66 4-7 Tufts Tennis Team, 1966; MS088.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Lacross 66 4-7 Tufts Lacross, 1966; MS088.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Baseball 66 4-7 Tufts Baseball, 1966; MS088.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Baseball 66 4-23 Joe O'Kelly, 1966; MS088.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Track 66 4-25, 1966; MS088.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. Golf Team, 1966; MS088.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. Sailing Team, 1966; MS088.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - 66 5-15 Tufts U. All-Sports Banquet, 1966; MS088.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Bell John P. Tilton, 1966; MS088.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Football Co-Captains and Coach, 1966; MS088.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Football Singles - Action Part 1, 1966; MS088.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Football Singles - Action Part 2, 1966; MS088.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Football Singles - Action Part 3, 1966; MS088.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - f 66 8-31 (#s 1-8) Tufts Football Coaches and Mouthguard Pics., 1966; MS088.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Tufts- Football Portraits Part 1, 1966; MS088.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Tufts- Football Portraits Part 2, 1966; MS088.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Tufts- Football Portraits Part 3, 1966; MS088.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Tufts - Re-shots of Football Co-Captains, 1966; MS088.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Cross-Country Team Soccer Team Sailing Team, 1966; MS088.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Basketball Posed Action Singles, 1966; MS088.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. Presentation of books to German Department by German Consul General, 1966; MS088.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. Photos of Jackson Parents Weekend -Reception for girls and parents at Curtis Hall -Noon meal at Jackson Gym. Part 1, 1966; MS088.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
    November 11 & 12, 1966
  - Tufts U. Photos of Jackson Parents Weekend -Reception for girls and parents at Curtis Hall -Noon meal at Jackson Gym. Part 2, 1966; MS088.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. Luncheon for Girls and Parents at Cousens Gym. Family in Football Stands. etc., 1966; MS088.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Tufts New 1967 Football Captain and Carzo., 1966; MS088.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Basketball vs. Northeastern, 1966; MS088.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Basketball Team, 1966; MS088.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. Gulf Oil Presentation, 1967; MS088.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. William Gillman, Tufts Student, 1967; MS088.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Gramp Pic, 1967; MS088.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Alumni Weekend Committee Meeting, 1967; MS088.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Swimming, 1967; MS088.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Wrestling, 1967; MS088.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Indoor Track, 1967; MS088.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - TuftsBasketball vs. Brandeis, 1967; MS088.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Tufts U. Red Cross Lifesaving Award to Lee Nordan by Pices, Meade, 1967; MS088.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - New England College wrestling championship at Tufts. 1 of 2, 1967; MS088.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - New England College wrestling championship at Tufts. 2 of 2, 1967; MS088.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Tufts - Rocky Carzo at desk., 1967; MS088.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. - 3 basketball players who hit 1000 mark., 1967; MS088.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Tufts - Civil Engineering project., 1967; MS088.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Tufts - Copy Reg. of Old Library., 1967; MS088.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Tufts All-Sports Banquet, 1967; MS088.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - "Beelzebubs" Vocal group at Tufts University., 1967; MS088.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. - Team photos: Baseball, lacrosse, trade, sailing, tennis, golf., 1967; MS088.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. - Northeastern State youth conference., 1967; MS088.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. - Northeastern State youth conference. (Extras), 1967; MS088.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Passport Pics of Mary - Pat Murane (Public Relations Office)., 1967; MS088.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U.: PR. Gramp Pic with Prof. McCarthy, 1967; MS088.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Tufts. Barnam Museum shots., 1967; MS088.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Tufts. digging up of the road., 1967; MS088.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Prof. Knipp program: Atomic energy pics, (bubble projects). etc., 1967; MS088.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
    September 13-14, 1967
  - Varsity Football team., 1967; MS088.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Bronze Star Presentation, 1967; MS088.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Burton C. Hallowell Inauguration, 1967; MS088.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Football Portraits. 1 of 2, 1967; MS088.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Football Portraits. 2 of 2, 1967; MS088.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Copy reg. for program cover., 1967; MS088.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Spofford Crawford Testimonial in Jackson Gym., 1967; MS088.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Macmillan Cup Team -Sailing., 1967; MS088.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Homecoming Queen (Football)., 1967; MS088.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Sailing Team, Soccer Team, Cross Country Team., 1967; MS088.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Basketball Captain and Coach for 1967-1968. Art Marquardt and Woody., MS088.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Arts in Africa, 1967; MS088.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. New (1968) Football Captains., 1967; MS088.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Soccer copy neg. for Dane Ertidge., 1967; MS088.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. PR. Debate team., 1967; MS088.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. PR. Prof. James J. McKeown Civil Engineering dept., 1967; MS088.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Basketball vs. Wheaton., 1967; MS088.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. PR. mobile Theater stage., 1967; MS088.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Boy Scouts, 1967; MS088.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Tufts U. Varsity, Basketball Team, Swimming team, Wrestling team., 1968; MS088.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Indoor Track team, 2-mile relay. fresh: relay., 1968; MS088.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Indoor Track Team, 1968; MS088.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. PR. Library Windows, 1968; MS088.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. PR. Beauty Contest - Contestants., 1968; MS088.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. PR. Winter weekend Queen, 1968; MS088.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Tufts basketball. New Captain and group pic (Seniors with Woody)., 1968; MS088.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Basketball Singles of Mike Smion(?), 1968; MS088.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Baseball and Lacrosse Team and Singles., 1968; MS088.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Civil Engineering Project by Students, 1968; MS088.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Team Pics. - Tennis, Track, Golf, Sailing., 1968; MS088.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Tufts PR. R.O.T.C. Award to Sandy Tredinnidi in Sweet Hall., 1968; MS088.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Sports, 1968; MS088.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Tufts -Graduate Student Gloria Barron., 1968; MS088.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Day Camp group Pic., 1968; MS088.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Football portraits -Unused., 1968; MS088.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Football portraits -used., 1968; MS088.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. X-Country team, Soccer team and individuals., 1968; MS088.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Football team., 1968; MS088.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Sailing Team, 1968; MS088.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Tufts Homecoming Queen, 1968; MS088.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Tufts PR - Check presentation, 1968; MS088.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. - Pictures of Robert McCowan at WHDH-TV. Tufts Lincoln Filene Center, 1968; MS088.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Rocky and Woody with Alan Herosian, John Gulesian, and John Avadision., 1968; MS088.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Track Coach "Ding" Dusault., 1968; MS088.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Sports. Basketball team. Swimming team. Wrestling team., 1968; MS088.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Sports. Baseball team. Lacrosse team. Track team. Sailing team., 1969; MS088.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Rick Giachetti Wedding in Wolloston., 1969; MS088.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Football portraits, 1969; MS088.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Football team. Sailing team. Soccer team., 1969; MS088.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Track team., 1967; MS088.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Grid Team Sit-in at President's Office., 1969; MS088.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. "Break-up Dinner" for Football Team., 1967; MS088.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Beelsbubs - Tufts University. Contact (Proof of each neg.), 1969; MS088.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Copy Negative of Vandersea., 1969; MS088.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Tufts U. Team Pictures. Basketball, Wrestling, Swimming, Track., 1970; MS088.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Tufts University. Copy Negative of American Alumni Council Award., 1970; MS088.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Tufts University. Football Team, 1970; MS088.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Tufts University.Sailing Team Picture, 1970; MS088.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Tufts University.Soccer Team. Cross-Country Team., 1970; MS088.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Tufts University.Varsity Basketball, Track Team Pictures., 1970; MS088.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Woody Grimshaw. Copy Negative of 1970 Tufts Golf Team., MS088.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Lacrosse Team., 1971; MS088.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Baseball Team., 1972; MS088.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Teams. Lacrosse, Golf, Sailing-men, Sailing-women, Swimming, Track, Cross-Country., 1972; MS088.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
    April- May 1972
  - Tufts U. "Athlete of the Year" Trophy to Dan Moynahan., 1972; MS088.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Police in cruiser. L-R. Louis Buccelli, Joe Masiello., 1972; MS088.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Football Team, 1972; MS088.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Soccer Team., 1972; MS088.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Tennis Single., 1973; MS088.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Teams. Tennis, Golf, Baseball, Cross-Country, Lacrosse, Track., 1973; MS088.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
    April - May 1973
  - Tufts U. Sailing trophy to individual., 1973; MS088.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Awarding letter "T" to Girl Athlete., 1973; MS088.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Golf Team, Tennis Team, Baseball Team, Lacrosse Team., 1974; MS088.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
    May 9-11, 1974
  - Copy Negative of old 19_ Tufts Baseball Team., MS088.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled. Basketball., MS088.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled. Basketball., MS088.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled. Basketball., MS088.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled. Basketball., MS088.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled. Basketball., MS088.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled. Basketball team., MS088.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Indoor Track, MS088.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Paul Rich - Unlabelled., MS088.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Tufts - Sailing National Title Pictures - Paul Rich, MS088.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Swimming, MS088.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Tufts U. Unlabelled Misc., MS088.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled Misc., MS088.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled., MS088.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled., MS088.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Unlabelled., MS088.001.006.00035 (Box 6)